Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Building Drawings and Large-Format Materials OS
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Collection of Building Drawings and Large-Format Materials
circa 1735-2013
New York University Archives
OS
8 flat file cases (plus 5 flat boxes and 87 oversize boxes)
This artificially constructed collection contains oversized and larger-scale materials from various University Archives collections, stored together in flat-file drawers and oversized boxes. This collection includes university building plans; NYU diplomas, certificates, and proclamations; photographs of buildings, student groups, University Presidents, and events; and NYU event posters.
Conditions Governing Access
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This is an artificial collection that contains oversized material drawn from an assortment of other University Archives collections. The accession numbers associated with this collection are 92.024, 2017.012, and 2020.035. A poster for an event hosted by the Institute for Afro-American Affairs was purchased in November 2021; the accession number associated with this purchase is 2022.018.
In April 2023, posters for animation festivals held for the Tisch School of the Arts were transferred from an accretion to the John Canemaker Papers MSS 040). The accession number associated with this transfer is 2023.022.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into 8 series:
Series I: Washington Square Area and Buildings
Series II: University Heights Area and Buildings
Series III: Other University Buildings
Series IV: Certificates, Diplomas, and Proclamations
Series V: Images and Photographs
Series VI: Clippings, Graphic Materials, and Printed Matter
Series VII: List of Collections for Separated Materials
Series VIII: Posters and Event Fliers
All contents are described in the finding aid except a portion of Series VIII: posters and event fliers, which are described in an Access database on the University Archives shared drive and cannot be accessed remotely.
Historical Note
The New York University Archives serves as the final repository for the historical records of NYU. Its primary purpose is to document the history of the University and to provide source material for administrators, faculty, students, alumni, and other members of the University community, as well as scholars, authors, and other interested persons who seek to evaluate the impact of the University's activities on the history of American social, cultural, and intellectual development.
Related Materials
Records of the Office of the University Architect, Joseph J. Roberto Collection (RG 11.4)
Washington Square Park (New York, NY) and Washington Square Area Image Collection, 1850-1990 (NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001)
Scope and Contents
Materials include larger-scale materials from various University Archives collections including university building plans; NYU diplomas, certificates, and proclamations; photographs of buildings, student groups, University Presidents, and events; and NYU event posters.
Architectural drawings (visual works); Architecture; Black-and-white photographs.; blueprints (reprographic copies); Certificates.; Clippings (information artifacts); Color photographs.; Diplomas.; Floor Plans (orthographic projections); Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.); Historic buildings -- New York (State) -- New York.; Posters.; Washington Square (New York, N.Y.); New York University. University Heights; Brademas, John, 1927-2016; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
- Series I: Washington Square Area and Buildings
  - Subseries A: Buildings
    - Campus buildings, block plan/map: Block 546 (West 4th Street and Mercer Street), September 22, 1964 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - Campus Map: Greenwich Village with historic sites and NYU buildings listed, 1959 (Box Shared University Archives 129)
    - Washington Square Campus overviews of buildings: photographs of artist renderings [2], 1949-1950 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
    - Unidentified Building: Artist Rendering (Walter C. Pfeiffer, Architect): color painting, undated (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Various Buildings (Faculty Office, unknown building): Engineering Plans, 1961-1968 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Plans: Bursar's Office, 1961 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Plans: Council Room, 1938 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Plans: Recorder's Office, 1959 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Plans: Theater, 1967 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Plans: Theater and Media Building, undated (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - 1 5th Avenue (Suite 18-G): Architectural Plans, circa 1960s-1970s (Flat-file-folder 1 Right)
    - 2 5th Avenue (Residences): Architectural Plans, circa 1960s (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - 85 West 3rd Street: Floor Plans (2), 1975 September 16-October 9 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - 89 West 3rd Street: Architectural Plans, August 5, 1970 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - 102 West 3rd Street: Architectural Plans, 1968-1970 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - 15-19 West 4th Street: floor plans for Army ROTC, Aerospace, Psychology Department rooms and demolition/construction plan of building, circa 1968 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - 510 West Broadway (144-146 Bleecker Street): Architectural Plans, March 1966 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - 684 Broadway: Architectural Plans, 1900s (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - 693 Broadway: Architectural Plans, 1899, 1965 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - 715 Broadway (1 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1971-1978 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - 285 Mercer Street: plans, 1994 (Flat-file-folder 3 Left)
    - University Place and 8th Street (Proposed): Architectural Plans by Walter Pfeiffer, 1900s (Flat-file-folder 6)
    - 1 University Place (Residences and Commercial Space): Architectural Plans, circa 1900s (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - 13-19 University Place (faculty office building): plans (2 folders), 1963-1969 (Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 8, Flat-file-folder 9)
    - 14 Washington Mews: Architectural Plans, 1966-1981 (Flat-file-folder 7)
    - 3-5 Washington Place: Blueprints, 1971 (Flat-file-folder 7)
    - 3-5 Washington Place (Fraternity Housing): Renovation Blueprints, 1979 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - 10 Washington Place: Architectural Plans, 1967-1986 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - 21 Washington Place: Architectural Plans, Artist Renderings, Proposed Site Uses, Proposed Remarque Memorial Library, 1964, 1978, 1984 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - 21 Washington Place: Artist Rendering (Eggers and Higgins, Architects): color painting of exterior, undated (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - 21 Washington Place: Alterations, Floor Plans, 1958-1976 (Flat-file-folder 6)
    - 23-29 Washington Place (Brown Building) building and floor plans, 1923-1964 (Flat-file-folder 6, Box Shared University Archives 056, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 5)
    - 23-29 Washington Place (Brown Building) building and floor plans/main block plans, 1962-1966 (Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 11, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 10, Box Shared University Archives 056, Folder 10)
    - 23-29 Washington Place (Brown Building): Architectural blueprints for fifth floor, undated (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - 24-26 Washington Place (NYU Bookstore): Remodeling Plan, 1947 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - 24-26 Washington Place (Press Annex Building): Architectural Plans, 1964, undated (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - 1-6 Washington Square North: building plans and sketches for Center for international Studies; the Dean's Room for Faculty of Arts and Science; etc., 1962-1976 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 12, Flat-file-folder 8)
    - 2 Washington Square North: 2nd floor, proposed Kosher kitchen, 1971 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 7)
      Separated Materials
      This blueprint was separated from box 17, folder 7 of the Records of the Jewish Culture Foundation, RG 12.11.
    - 3 Washington Square North: Artist's Rendering of a fireplace originally from Tours, France, undated (Box Shared University Archives 145, Folder 9)
      Original Location: Records of the Office of the University Architect, Joseph J. Roberto Collection (RG 11.4)
    - 7-13 Washington Square North: Architectural Plans, 1939 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - 14 Washington Square North (Residences): Architectural Plans, circa 1960s (Flat-file-folder 6)
    - 37 Washington Square North: Blueprints, Floor Plans by Robert Turner, Interior Views, undated (Flat-file 5, Drawer 6)
    - 50-60 Washington Square South: Artist's Rendering by Joseph J. Roberto, undated (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - 51 Washington Square South: Floor Plans, 1946 July (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - 29 Washington Square West: plan of patio and typical floor plan, 1985 (Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 1)
    - 37 Washington Square West: architectural plans, schedules, 1962-1969 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - 79 Washington Square East: Photo, April 16, 1970 (Box Shared University Archives 046, Folder 1)
    - 10 Waverly Place: second floor plan, undated (Flat-file-folder 3 Right)
    - 16 Waverly Place ("Upstairs at Harout's"): Architectural Plans for Library space, circa 1900s (Box Shared University Archives 047, Folder 6)
    - 28-30 Waverly Place: Drawing Extension, undated (Box Shared University Archives 127)
    - 170 Waverly Place: Blueprints, Floor Plans by H.T. Graves [Assoc.], Interior Sketches, April 16, 1974 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - 249 Greene Street color drawing, 1960s (Flat-file 6, Drawer 6)
    - Study of West Broadway from Houston to West 4th Street, July 13, 1965 (Flat-file-folder 3)
      This study was separated from Records of the Office of Administration and Facilities (Eileen Buckley), RG 8.0, Box 42
    - 528-30 West Broadway (at Bleecker Street): Architectural Plans, 1962 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Andre and Bella Meyer Physics Building (707 Broadway; 2-4 Washington Place; 4-6 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1962-1965 (Flat-file-folder 6)
    - Andre and Bella Meyer Physics Building (707 Broadway; 2-4 Washington Place; 4-6 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1965 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Andre and Bella Meyer Physics Building (707 Broadway; 2-4 Washington Place; 4-6 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1962-1963 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Andre and Bella Meyer Physics Building (707 Broadway; 2-4 Washington Place; 4-6 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1965-1966 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Andre and Bella Meyer Physics Building (707 Broadway; 2-4 Washington Place; 4-6 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1962-1966 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Biology Department Center (721-727 Broadway): Architectural Plans, 1978 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Brittany House; Hotel Brittany (55 East 10th Street): Architectural Plans, 1966 (Box Shared University Archives 047, Folder 5)
    - Brittany Residence Hall; Hotel Brittany (55 East 10th Street): Architectural Plans (3 folders), 1968-1975, 1992 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Broadway Central Hotel (673 Broadway): Architectural Plans, 1960-1962 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Carlyle Court Dormitory Buildings (21 East 15th St. and 20 East 16th St.) plans, 1986 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 12)
    - Carlyle Court Dormitory Buildings (21 East 15th St. and 20 East 16th St.) plans, 1986, 1988 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 12)
    - Center for Jewish Culture, Proposed (West Broadway and West 3rd Street): Architectural Plans, 1963-1964 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Chancellor's Residence (34 West 11th Street): Architectural Plans, 1967 (Flat-file-folder 8)
    - Coles Sports and Recreation Center: building plans (2), 1979 (Box 22)
    - Coles Sports and Recreation Center, undated (Box 22)
    - Coles Sports and Recreation Center: Sketches and plans, 1965, 1970 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Athletic Facility (Washington Square), Recreation Center, Physical Fitness Center (Coles Center?): plans from various architecture firms (proposals?), 1967-1970 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Commerce Building and Shimkin Hall: building and floor plans, 1961-1965 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Commerce Building and Shimkin Hall: building and floor plans, 1965-1966 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Commerce Building/Shimkin Hall: architectural plans, 1973 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Computing Facility: Architectural Plans, 1975 (Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Conservation Center (14 East 78th Street): analysis of space, floor cross sections, 1978 (Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Dean's Apartment: Floor Plans, 1964, 1968 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Deutsches Haus (Department of Germanic Languages and Literature): plans, 2 folders, 1975-1976 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Dreyfus Hall of Science: photograph of artist rendering (Eggers and Higgins, Architects), 1949 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
    - Dreyfus Hall of Science: Artist Renderings (Walter C. Pfeiffer, Architect), undated (Flat-file 2, Drawer 14)
    - East Building (239 Greene Street): plans, 1966-1970 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Education Building (35-41 West 4th Street and Greene Street): floor plans for 7th floor and basement, 1929 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Education Building: plans, proposals, 1960-1968 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Education Building (35-41 West 4th Street and Greene Street): architectural plans, 1962-1963 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Education Building: proposed floor plans, artist color sketches of spaces and photograph of building model (are mounted on 22 boards), circa 1963 (Drawer 4)
    - Faculty Club (22 Washington Square North): Architectural Plans, 1963, 1969 (Flat-file-folder 6)
    - Farkas Hall (Schools of Education and Social Work) at Washington Square East, Washington Place, West 4th Street: proposed plans-3 folders, 1965-1971 (Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 6)
    - Founders' Monument: Artist Renderings, 1977 and undated (Box Shared University Archives 122)
    - Furman Hall (Law School): Colored Artist's Renderings from different viewpoints, one through the Arch, circa 2000-2004 (Box Shared University Archives 122, Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East), Stern Residence Hall, Students Building (51 West 4th Street): Plan Compilations, 1983-1984 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East), Stern Residence Hall, Students Building (51 West 4th Street): Basement, Cellar, and 1st Floor, 1983-1985 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 6)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East), Stern Residence Hall, Students Building (51 West 4th Street): Floors 2-7, Roof plans, 1983-1986 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 8)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East) Students Building: Sectional and Elevation Views, exterior views, sketches interior, 1983-1984 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East), Stern Residence Hall, Students Building (51 West 4th Street): various floor plans of rooms, dining rooms, lounges, lobbies, etc., 1984 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East), Stern Residence Hall, Students Building (51 West 4th Street): Cafe and Violet Cafe floor plans, 1984-1985 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East), Stern Residence Hall, Students Building (51 West 4th Street): Interior Components, Details, Systems (doors, windows, ducts), 1984-1986 (Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Leonard Stern Student Residence Hall, later renamed Goddard Hall (80 Washington Square East): plans (7 folders), 1985-1986 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 6)
    - Graduate Student Residence Hall (26th Street and 1st Avenue), undated (Flat-file 3, Drawer 13)
    - Hayden Hall (33 Washington Square West): floor plans, renovation proposal, 1955, 1965, 1969 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Hayden Hall and Vanderbilt Hall: Artist Renderings (Eggers and Higgins, Architects), circa 1947-1952 (Box 1)
    - Hayden Hall (33 Washington Square West): Artwork for publications, circa 1990s-2000s (Box Shared University Archives 122)
    - Health Services third and fourth floor plans (laminated sheets), March 5, 1997 (Box 22)
    - Heyman Hall: Artist's Renderings, 1967 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - Judson Memorial Church: exterior plans/elevations, cross-sections, color drawings of exterior, undated (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Judson Residence Hall plans (1 of 2), 1947, 1977 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Judson Residence Hall plans (2 of 2), 1947, 1977 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 16)
    - Kevorkian Center (50 Washington Square South): Architectural Plans and sketches (2 folders), 1967-1978 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Kevorkian Center (50 Washington Square South): Artist Rendering, undated (Box 38)
    - Kevorkian Center: Artists rendering, 1960s (Flat-file-folder 6)
    - Kevorkian Center wood and gilt molding sample, 1972 (Box 8)
    - Kimball Hall (22 Waverly Place; 246 Greene Street): Exterior rendering, Architectural Plans, 1962 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Kimmel Center architectural plans book, 1999 (Box 21)
    - Kimmel Center: graphics of shadow impact analysis, mounted on foam core, 1999 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Kimmel Center: floor/building plans (2 folders), 1999-2002 (Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 4, Box Shared University Archives 058, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Kimmel Center: color artist renderings of front and sides of building, mounted on foam core (2 folders), 2000 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Kimmel Center: floor plans, etc., 2000 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Kimmel Center: Fabric Swatch Board, 2001 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Kimmel Center - Catering on the Square and The Market Place Cafe, undated (Box 21)
    - La Maison Francaise (15-16 Washington Mews): Architectural Plans for first floor, February 13, 1978 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - La Maison Francaise (15-16 Washington Mews): Architectural Plans, 1956-1977 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - La Maison Francaise (15-16 Washington Mews): Artist Rendering, undated (Box Shared University Archives 122)
    - Law School: Vanderbilt Hall, North Forecourt plans, 1967 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Law Center (Law Library, Vanderbilt Hall): plans, 1963-1983 (Flat-file-folder 7, Box Shared University Archives 058, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 8, Flat-file-folder 6 Left)
    - Law Center: Artwork for publications, circa 1990s-2000s (Box Shared University Archives 122)
    - Loeb Student Center: floorplan blueprints mounted on boards, 1955-1956 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 6)
    - Loeb Student Center: floor plans, 1957, 1964-1965 (Flat-file-folder 8, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 7)
    - Loeb Student Center: NYU Photo Bureau Prints (6), 1963 and 1970 (Box 1)
    - Musical Theater Hall of Fame: floor plans, 1993 (Flat-file-folder 3 Right)
    - NYU Mitchell-Lama Apartments and Washington Square Apartments: Site Development Costs, circa 1940s-1960s (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - NYU Redesign: Artist Renderings (Walter C. Pfeiffer, Architect), undated (Flat-file 2, Drawer 14)
    - Palladium Hall Athletic Facility Site: Furniture Layouts, circa 1995-2001 (Flat-file-folder 3)
    - Physical Science Building: plans, 1965 (Flat-file-folder 3 Right)
    - Proposed Class Room Building [East of Commerce]: Architectural Study, circa 1959 (Box 38)
    - Proposed plans: New Library (Warner, Burns, Toan, Lunde, Architects), plans and exterior sketches/artist rendering, 1963 (Flat-file 8, Drawer 15)
    - Proposed: Puerto Rican Cultural Center, 1961-1962 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Reading Consortium (87 West 3rd Street): Demolition and Architectural Plan, 1976 January 26-April 16 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - Renaissance House (160 Bleecker Street): Architectural Plans and Brochure, 1947, 1961 (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Research Library: photographs (2) of artist rendering (Eggers and Higgins, Architects) *in two separate folders in drawer*, 1952 (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
    - Research Library: Artist Renderings (Walter C. Pfeiffer, Architect), undated (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
    - Rubin Residence Hall plans (formerly Grosvenor Hotel) plans, 1948-1979 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 15)
    - Rubin Residence Hall: Demolition Plans, Floor Plans, Sketches of 2nd Floor, May 26, 1969 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - School of Education: Artist Renderings, painting and pastel sketch (Perkins and Will, Architects), undated (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
    - Silver Towers (University Plaza, University Village): plans, artist renderings of exterior, 1964 (Flat-file-folder 6)
    - South Building (43-51 West 4th Street): architectural plans, 1947-1983 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Student Center (West Broadway and West 3rd Street): Architectural Plans, March 4, 1954 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Student Center: Artist Renderings, undated (Flat-file 2, Drawer 14)
    - Students Building (80 Washington Square East), later Stern, then Goddard Hall: architectural plans, 1947, 1984 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Students Building (80 Washington Square East): Floor Plans, 1963 June 13 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    - Tisch Hall: Artist's Rendering of exterior, 1960s (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
    - Tisch Hall and Gould Plaza: floor plans (3 folders), 1968, 1972, undated (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Tisch School of the Arts: construction blueprint plans/documents, plans for film theater, and design development building plans, 1966, 1980, 1984 (Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 8, Box Shared University Archives 056, Folder 8)
    - Tisch Hall: Artist Rendering color painting by Randolph Assoc., undated (Flat-file 5, Drawer 10)
    - University Main Building (100 Washington Square East) proposed renovations, not Implemented, by McKim, Mead and White), March 13, 1893 (Flat-file-folder 2 Right)
    - University Main Building (100 Washington Square East): floor plans for Grey Art Gallery's State Faire Art Gallery, 1971 (Flat-file-folder 6, Box Shared University Archives 056, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 5)
    - University Main Building (100 Washington Square East): Architectural Drawings and renderings of Grey Art Gallery at NYU, from William C Shopsin AIA & Giorgio Cavaglieri Faia Associated Architects, 1974 (Flat-file-folder 6, Box Shared University Archives 056, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 5)
    - University Main Building (100 Washington Square East): preliminary floor plans for Fine Arts Department Library, 1977-1978 (Flat-file-folder 6, Box Shared University Archives 056, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 5)
    - University Main Building: Exterior Photograph of Entrance, circa 1980s (Flat-file 5, Drawer 16)